<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Avinity Alive</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">open_drawer</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">close_drawer</string>

    <!-- Navigation Drawer menu labels -->
    <string name="nav_home">Home</string>


    <!-- Toolbar titles when navigation menu item is selected -->
    <string-array name="nav_item_activity_titles">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>My Profile</item>
        <item>Team Members</item>
        <item>Search Team</item>
        <item>Notice</item>
        <item>Video Vault</item>
        <item>Most Nominated</item>
        <item>Recent Recognition</item>
        <item>Support</item>
        <item>Logout</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="activity_title_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="activity_title_programme_overview">Programme Overview</string>
    <string name="activity_title_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="action_clear_all">Clear All</string>
    <string name="action_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="action_mark_all_read">Mark All as Read</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="recognize_detail_info">

You can recognise your colleagues for living our values and going the extra mile.\n\n

You will have a budget of 60 points per month that you can award to your colleagues in recognition of their extraordinary work. They will receive an email letting them know they were recognised and your nomination will also appear on the time wall for others to like or comment.\n\n

When you receive nominations, these will fill up your recognition pillar. As soon as your recognition pillar is 100% complete, you are entitled to an additional day off. Please liaise with your manager to redeem this.\n\n

    </string>


    <string name="content_my_kudos">For each pillar you achieve 100%, the Kudos Club will reward you with 100 Kudos Points to redeem against your catalogue.\nFurthermore, complete more pillars to grow your KudosBank balance!\n</string>

    <string name="content_team_kudos">Here you can see how your functional team is doing – some colleagues may need a bit of motivation! Also check out the Ranking section to see where you team currently stands. Note that points collected in team challenges go straight into your individual Kudos Bank.</string>

    <string name="challenge_info">The Kudos Club rewards you for getting involved.\n\nBy completing challenges you can fill up our Value pillars. Once a pillar is full, you earn yourself Kudos Points to spend in our online reward catalogue. The challenges are split between Easy, Medium and Difficult, depending on the amount of time involved. You can also choose between taking a challenge yourself or work with your team.\n\nThe challenges show the % of that Value Pillar you will fill once you complete the activity, so go on; pick a few now that you will commit to do, and good luck.</string>
    <string name="content_recognize_header">Recognition nominations can either be £0 value e-cards, or nominees can receive time/points to redeem against the catalogue. You decide.</string>


    <string name="main_action_crop">CROP</string>
    <string name="main_action_rotate">Rotate 90 degrees clockwise</string>
    <string name="result_image_desc">crop result</string>
    <string name="label_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="label_ok">Ok</string>

</resources>
